Welcome to Vibe Sentinel, the agentic reliability layer for fast-moving project teams.
In the next four minutes, I will show the complete workflow from first audit to submission-ready output.
The goal is simple: keep the speed of vibe coding, but remove the risk of shipping a fragile demo.
We start on the Tutorial page.
This page is intentionally concise and marketing-forward.
A beginner can immediately understand the product promise, the three-step loop, and the value they will get in the first run.
The score cards show a realistic before-and-after story, and the call to action moves directly into the working dashboard.
Now we open the Dashboard.
This is the operational home for the full lifecycle.
At the top, we set a project path.
Then we use the beginner lane first.
Run Audit is the baseline check, and Launch Ship Sequence is the one-command path to improve project quality.
Everything else can stay hidden until the user is ready.
I start the built-in beginner tutorial.
This creates a guided sequence with visible progress, so new users know exactly what to do next.
No guessing.
No reading long docs first.
Just a concrete path from zero to an improved score.
Now we run the baseline audit.
Vibe Sentinel scans the repo and scores usefulness, impact, execution, and innovation.
It also identifies practical blockers like missing tests, weak documentation, absent CI, and artifact gaps.
The point is not to produce noise.
The point is to create an ordered, fixable plan.
After the audit finishes, we scroll through the score breakdown and recommendations.
You can immediately see where the project is weak and what actions provide the highest lift.
This is critical in hackathon settings, where teams do not have time to manually triage dozens of quality issues.
Next, I enable advanced actions and run them one by one.
Agent Pack turns findings into structured tasks for coding agents.
Coach generates beginner-friendly fix cards in plain language.
Roadmap generates a practical sequence so improvements happen in the right order.
These outputs reduce context switching between humans and agents.
Now we launch the full Ship Sequence.
This orchestrates the complete improvement loop:
audit, task generation, coaching, roadmap, safe starter files, and re-check.
Instead of running multiple commands manually, teams execute one workflow and keep momentum.
This is where Vibe Sentinel becomes a true killer app for agentic development.
After Ship Sequence completes, we start Demo Tour mode.
Demo Tour automatically highlights the narrative flow for recordings and live presentations.
It gives you a stable, repeatable story:
score story, findings, tasks, artifacts, and timeline.
That means less presentation chaos and a more credible demo under pressure.
Now we move to the Artifacts page.
This page is focused and fast.
You can refresh artifacts from audit, run ship plus refresh, and preview generated outputs in one place.
Everything needed for judges is centralized:
report files, coaching output, roadmap, and agent prompts.
No hunting through folders while screen sharing.
From here, I trigger another refresh and ship cycle.
This shows that the flow is repeatable, not a one-time scripted success.
A reliable process is the real differentiator in competitions.
Anyone can generate code quickly.
Far fewer teams can prove consistent execution quality.
Next we open the OpenClaw page.
This is the bridge for external agent orchestration over HTTP.
I set the project path, probe bridge status, and run an action through the bridge endpoint.
You can also copy cURL or JSON request payloads for automation workflows.
This makes Vibe Sentinel useful beyond a single UI session.
Finally, we return to the Tutorial page.
This closes the loop between discoverability and execution.
The tutorial communicates the value clearly, and the studio proves it with real outputs and score movement.
If you are building with coding agents, this is the core advantage:
Vibe Sentinel gives you deterministic checkpoints, structured handoff, and submission-ready artifacts without slowing down creative velocity.
You still build fast.
You just ship with confidence.